https://primmart.com/privacy-policy/

HomeAboutPrimitive Decorating – What is Primitive?Work with MeBlogNewsletterNewsletter Resource LibraryFree Primitive PatternsCraft SuppliesBusiness ResourcesContact UsPrivacy PolicyTerms of Use Skip to primary navigation Skip to main content Skip to primary sidebar Skip to footerHome Design & ManagementDecor & DesignCleaning & OrganizingHome Maintenance & ImprovementBuying, Selling & Moving HomesHome ValueElectrical & Energy UseHeating & CoolingPest ControlPlumbingRoof MaintenanceSecurityTools & EquipmentOutdoor LivingGardeningLandscapingLawn CarePatio DecoratingDaily LifeFamilyFamily FinancesPetsIn The KitchenBeauty & FashionCar Care & MoreEducationRelationshipsSafetySelf ImprovementWellnessWork & BusinessLeisure & TravelCelebrations & HolidaysCraftsFamily FunShoppingTravelShow SearchSearch this website Hide SearchHome » Privacy PolicyWho we areOur website address is: https://primmart.com.What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsThe data is captured when someone submits a contact form included their name, email, and website address. We keep contact form submissions for a period of 3 months for customer service purposes. We do not use the information submitted through them for marketing purposes.CookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.Social MediaWe embed a Facebook widget to allow you to see number of likes/shares/recommends and “like/share/recommend” our webpages. This widget may collect your IP address, your web browser User Agent, store and retrieve cookies on your browser, embed additional tracking, and monitor your interaction with the widget, including correlating your Facebook account with whatever action you take within the widget (such as “liking/sharing/recommending” our webpage), if you are logged in to Facebook. For more information about how this data may be used, please see Facebook’s data privacy policy: https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/update.We use a GooglePlus widget at our website. As a result, our website makes requests to Google’s servers for you to be able to share our webpages using your GooglePlus account. These requests make your IP address visible to Google, who may use it in accordance with their data privacy policy: https://policies.google.com/privacyWe use Pinterest Save widget at our website to allow you to pin images to Pinterest from our webpages. These requests may track your IP address in accordance with their data privacy policy: https://policy.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy.We use StumbleUpon Badge widget at our website which may log information when you interact with the widget. Log Data is a form of Non-Identifying Information, in accordance with their privacy policy: http://www.stumbleupon.com/privacyWe use a Twitter Tweet widget at our website. As a result, our website makes requests to Twitter’s servers for you to be able to tweet our webpages using your Twitter account. These requests make your IP address visible to Twitter, who may use it in accordance with their data privacy policy: https://twitter.com/en/privacy#update.AnalyticsWho we share your data withData is shared with Google analytics to keep track of our website traffic (age, region of world, male or female).Data is sent to third parties that help us track traffic on our site. This includes clicking on advertising links and affiliate links. Data may include the products purchased through the link, the amount paid, and/or demographics (age, region of world, male or female). Thirds parties include: Amazon, Google Adsense, ShareASale, Awin, Rakuten, CJ, Linkshare, Chicory, Flex Offers, Max Bounty, VigLinks, Skim Links.How long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.How long we keep data: contact form entries for three months, analytics records for a year, and customer purchase records for ten years.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.Where we send your dataVisitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.Your contact informationYour contact information is stored securely and used only for the said purpose in which it was given: a contact inquiry, a purchase, or subscribing to our newsletter. The only time you will receive emails is to respond in the appropriate manner for which it was received. We will not add you to our newsletter unless you request it. You may unsubscribe at anytime or ask to do so for you.If you have a business and would like to be included in our business directory, we will collect your contact information: name, email, business name, website address. In order to correspond with you to create your business listing. We store this contact information for as long as your business is listed in order for us to contact you for future updates to listing. This contact information is kept securely on a computer and cloud storage and/or external hard drive as backups.Additional informationHow we protect your dataWe have software in place to keep all data safe and secure including a security wall to keep unwanted parties from accessing the website's data records.What data breach procedures we have in placeSecurity software alerts us to any login or access attempts that are unauthorized. The software blocks these unwanted parties from being able to login and access any records.What third parties we receive data fromWe receive data through third parties that help us track traffic on our site. This includes clicking on advertising links and affiliate links. Data may include the products purchased through the link, the amount paid, and/or demographics (age, region of world, male or female). Thirds parties include: Amazon, Google Adsense, ShareASale, Awin, Rakuten, CJ, Linkshare, Chicory, Flex Offers, Max Bounty, VigLinks, Skim Links.What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user dataAdsense and Amazon ads that are shown on our site are chosen automatically based on your user data, as in your browser history. To put this simply, if you've been browsing the web for a new lamp, you will start seeing lamp ads on our site.Purchase DataWe collect information about you during the checkout process on our store.What we collect and storeWhile you visit our site, we’ll track:Products you’ve viewed: we’ll use this to, for example, show you products you’ve recently viewedLocation, IP address and browser type: we’ll use this for purposes like estimating taxes and shippingShipping address: we’ll ask you to enter this so we can, for instance, estimate shipping before you place an order, and send you the order!We’ll also use cookies to keep track of cart contents while you’re browsing our site.When you purchase from us, we’ll ask you to provide information including your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, phone number, credit card/payment details and optional account information like username and password. We’ll use this information for purposes, such as, to:Send you information about your account and orderRespond to your requests, including refunds and complaintsProcess payments and prevent fraudSet up your account for our storeComply with any legal obligations we have, such as calculating taxesImprove our store offeringsSend you marketing messages, if you choose to receive themIf you create an account, we will store your name, address, email and phone number, which will be used to populate the checkout for future orders.We generally store information about you for as long as we need the information for the purposes for which we collect and use it, and we are not legally required to continue to keep it. For example, we will store order information for XXX years for tax and accounting purposes. This includes your name, email address and billing and shipping addresses.We will also store comments or reviews, if you choose to leave them.Who on our team has accessMembers of our team have access to the information you provide us. For example, both Administrators and Shop Managers can access:Order information like what was purchased, when it was purchased and where it should be sent, andCustomer information like your name, email address, and billing and shipping information.Our team members have access to this information to help fulfill orders, process refunds and support you.What we share with othersPaymentsWe accept payments through PayPal. When processing payments, some of your data will be passed to PayPal, including information required to process or support the payment, such as the purchase total and billing information.Please see the PayPal Privacy Policy for more details.Primary SidebarSearch for SomethingSearch this websiteSince 2001 Prim Mart has been the place for those who enjoy the country life. Home decorating ideas, home improvement tips, gardening inspiration, craft tutorials, and much more. Read More…EmailFacebookPinterestRecent Posts 4 Essential Plumbing Maintenance Projects to Do Every Couple Years 3 Indoor Activities to Try During Winter How Smart Technology Revolutionized Modern Garage Doors 6 Natural Oils That Have Amazing Skin Care Benefits 5 Things You Might Do After Filing for Long-Term Disability BenefitsCategoriesCategoriesSelect CategoryDaily Life   Beauty & Fashion   Car Care & More   Education   Family   Family Finances   In The Kitchen   Pets   Relationships   Safety   Self Improvement   Technology   Wellness   Work & BusinessHome Design & Management   Buying, Selling & Moving Homes   Cleaning & Organizing   Decor & DesignHome Maintenance & Improvement   Electrical & Energy Use   Heating & Cooling   Home Appliances   Home Value   Pest Control   Plumbing   Roof Maintenance   Security   Tools & EquipmentLeisure & Travel   Celebrations & Holidays   Crafts   Family Fun   Nature   Shopping   TravelOutdoor Living   Farming   Gardening   Landscaping   Lawn Care   Patio DecoratingPopular PostsRoundupsUncategorized
FooterCategoriesCategoriesSelect CategoryDaily Life   Beauty & Fashion   Car Care & More   Education   Family   Family Finances   In The Kitchen   Pets   Relationships   Safety   Self Improvement   Technology   Wellness   Work & BusinessHome Design & Management   Buying, Selling & Moving Homes   Cleaning & Organizing   Decor & DesignHome Maintenance & Improvement   Electrical & Energy Use   Heating & Cooling   Home Appliances   Home Value   Pest Control   Plumbing   Roof Maintenance   Security   Tools & EquipmentLeisure & Travel   Celebrations & Holidays   Crafts   Family Fun   Nature   Shopping   TravelOutdoor Living   Farming   Gardening   Landscaping   Lawn Care   Patio DecoratingPopular PostsRoundupsUncategorized
MenuHomeAboutBlogAdvertisingContact UsTerms of UsePrivacy PolicyArchives Archives Select Month December 2020 November 2020 October 2020 September 2020 August 2020 July 2020 June 2020 May 2020 April 2020 March 2020 February 2020 January 2020 December 2019 November 2019 October 2019 September 2019 August 2019 July 2019 June 2019 May 2019 April 2019 March 2019 February 2019 January 2019 December 2018 November 2018 October 2018 September 2018 August 2018 July 2018 June 2018 May 2018 April 2018 March 2018 February 2018 January 2018 November 2017 August 2017 July 2017 June 2017 July 2014 March 2014 February 2014 November 2013
This website or its third-party tools use cookies, which are necessary to its functioning and required to achieve the purposes illustrated in the cookie policy. If you want to know more or withdraw your consent to all or some of the cookies, please refer to the cookie policy on our Privacy Policy Page. By closing this banner, scrolling this page, clicking a link or continuing to browse otherwise, you agree to the use of cookies.OkPrivacy Policy
